{
  "name": "1000_mots",
  "voice_2": null,
  "number": "1",
  "voice_1": null,
  "introduction": null,
  "pul_elements": [
    {
      "answer": "as",
      "question": "comme",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "I",
      "question": "je",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "his",
      "question": "son",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "that",
      "question": "que",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "he",
      "question": "il",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "was",
      "question": "était",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "for",
      "question": "pour",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "on",
      "question": "sur",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "are",
      "question": "sont",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "with",
      "question": "avec",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "they",
      "question": "ils",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "be",
      "question": "être",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "at",
      "question": "à",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "one",
      "question": "un",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "have",
      "question": "avoir",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "this",
      "question": "ce",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "from",
      "question": "à partir de",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "by",
      "question": "par",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "hot",
      "question": "chaud",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "word",
      "question": "mot",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "but",
      "question": "mais",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "what",
      "question": "que",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "some",
      "question": "certains",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "is",
      "question": "est",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "it",
      "question": "il",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "you",
      "question": "vous",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "or",
      "question": "ou",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "had",
      "question": "eu",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "the",
      "question": "la",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "of",
      "question": "de",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "to",
      "question": "à",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "and",
      "question": "et",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "a",
      "question": "un",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "in",
      "question": "dans",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "we",
      "question": "nous",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "can",
      "question": "boîte",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "out",
      "question": "dehors",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "other",
      "question": "autre",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "were",
      "question": "étaient",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "which",
      "question": "qui",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "do",
      "question": "faire",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "their",
      "question": "leur",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "time",
      "question": "temps",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "if",
      "question": "si",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "will",
      "question": "volonté",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "how",
      "question": "comment",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "said",
      "question": "dit",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "an",
      "question": "un",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "each",
      "question": "chaque",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "tell",
      "question": "dire",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "set",
      "question": "ensemble",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "three",
      "question": "trois",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "want",
      "question": "vouloir",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "air",
      "question": "air",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "well",
      "question": "bien",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "also",
      "question": "aussi",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "play",
      "question": "jouer",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "small",
      "question": "petit",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "end",
      "question": "fin",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "put",
      "question": "mettre",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "home",
      "question": "maison",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "read",
      "question": "lire",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "hand",
      "question": "main",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "port",
      "question": "port",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "large",
      "question": "grand",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "spell",
      "question": "épeler",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "add",
      "question": "ajouter",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "even",
      "question": "même",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "land",
      "question": "terre",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "here",
      "question": "ici",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "must",
      "question": "il faut",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "big",
      "question": "grand",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "high",
      "question": "haut",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "such",
      "question": "tel",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "follow",
      "question": "suivre",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "act",
      "question": "acte",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "why",
      "question": "pourquoi",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "ask",
      "question": "interroger",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "men",
      "question": "hommes",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "change",
      "question": "changement",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "went",
      "question": "est allé",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "light",
      "question": "lumière",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "kind",
      "question": "genre",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "off",
      "question": "de",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "need",
      "question": "besoin",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "house",
      "question": "maison",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "picture",
      "question": "image",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "try",
      "question": "essayer",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "us",
      "question": "nous",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "again",
      "question": "encore",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "animal",
      "question": "animal",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "point",
      "question": "point",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "mother",
      "question": "mère",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "world",
      "question": "monde",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "near",
      "question": "près de",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "build",
      "question": "construire",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "self",
      "question": "soi",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "earth",
      "question": "terre",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "father",
      "question": "père",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "any",
      "question": "tout",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "new",
      "question": "nouveau",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "work",
      "question": "travail",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "part",
      "question": "partie",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "take",
      "question": "prendre",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "get",
      "question": "obtenir",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "place",
      "question": "lieu",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "made",
      "question": "fabriqué",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "live",
      "question": "vivre",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "where",
      "question": "où",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "after",
      "question": "après",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "back",
      "question": "arrière",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "little",
      "question": "peu",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "only",
      "question": "seulement",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "round",
      "question": "tour",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "man",
      "question": "homme",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "year",
      "question": "année",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "came",
      "question": "est venu",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "show",
      "question": "montrer",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "every",
      "question": "tous",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "good",
      "question": "bon",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "me",
      "question": "moi",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "give",
      "question": "donner",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "our",
      "question": "notre",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "under",
      "question": "sous",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "name",
      "question": "nom",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "very",
      "question": "très",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "through",
      "question": "par",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "just",
      "question": "juste",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "form",
      "question": "forme",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "sentence",
      "question": "phrase",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "great",
      "question": "grand",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "think",
      "question": "penser",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "say",
      "question": "dire",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "help",
      "question": "aider",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "low",
      "question": "faible",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "line",
      "question": "ligne",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "differ",
      "question": "différer",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "turn",
      "question": "tour",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "cause",
      "question": "la cause",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "much",
      "question": "beaucoup",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "mean",
      "question": "signifier",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "before",
      "question": "avant",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "move",
      "question": "déménagement",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "right",
      "question": "droit",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "boy",
      "question": "garçon",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "old",
      "question": "vieux",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "too",
      "question": "trop",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "same",
      "question": "même",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "she",
      "question": "elle",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "all",
      "question": "tous",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "there",
      "question": "là",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "when",
      "question": "quand",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "up",
      "question": "jusqu’à",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "use",
      "question": "utiliser",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "your",
      "question": "votre",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "way",
      "question": "manière",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "about",
      "question": "sur",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "many",
      "question": "beaucoup",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "then",
      "question": "puis",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "them",
      "question": "les",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "write",
      "question": "écrire",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "would",
      "question": "voudrais",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "like",
      "question": "comme",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "so",
      "question": "si",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "these",
      "question": "ces",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "her",
      "question": "son",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "long",
      "question": "long",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "make",
      "question": "faire",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "thing",
      "question": "chose",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "see",
      "question": "voir",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "him",
      "question": "lui",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "two",
      "question": "deux",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "has",
      "question": "a",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "look",
      "question": "regarder",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "more",
      "question": "plus",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "day",
      "question": "jour",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "could",
      "question": "pourrait",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "go",
      "question": "aller",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "come",
      "question": "venir",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "did",
      "question": "fait",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "number",
      "question": "nombre",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "sound",
      "question": "son",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "no",
      "question": "aucun",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "most",
      "question": "plus",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "people",
      "question": "personnes",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "my",
      "question": "ma",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "over",
      "question": "sur",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "know",
      "question": "savoir",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "water",
      "question": "eau",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "than",
      "question": "que",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "call",
      "question": "appel",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "first",
      "question": "première",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "who",
      "question": "qui",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "may",
      "question": "peut",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "down",
      "question": "vers le bas",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "side",
      "question": "côté",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "been",
      "question": "été",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "now",
      "question": "maintenant",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "find",
      "question": "trouver",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "head",
      "question": "tête",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "stand",
      "question": "supporter",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "own",
      "question": "propre",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "page",
      "question": "page",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "should",
      "question": "devrait",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "country",
      "question": "pays",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "found",
      "question": "trouvé",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "answer",
      "question": "réponse",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "school",
      "question": "école",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "grow",
      "question": "croître",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "study",
      "question": "étude",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "still",
      "question": "encore",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "learn",
      "question": "apprendre",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "plant",
      "question": "usine",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "cover",
      "question": "couvercle",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "food",
      "question": "nourriture",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "sun",
      "question": "soleil",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "four",
      "question": "quatre",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "between",
      "question": "entre",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "state",
      "question": "état",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "keep",
      "question": "garder",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "eye",
      "question": "œil",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "never",
      "question": "jamais",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "last",
      "question": "dernier",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "let",
      "question": "laisser",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "thought",
      "question": "pensée",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "city",
      "question": "ville",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "tree",
      "question": "arbre",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "cross",
      "question": "traverser",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "farm",
      "question": "ferme",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "hard",
      "question": "dur",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "start",
      "question": "début",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "might",
      "question": "puissance",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "story",
      "question": "histoire",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "saw",
      "question": "scie",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "far",
      "question": "loin",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "sea",
      "question": "mer",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "draw",
      "question": "tirer",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "left",
      "question": "gauche",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "late",
      "question": "tard",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "run",
      "question": "courir",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "don’t",
      "question": "needs a context",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "while",
      "question": "tandis que",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "press",
      "question": "presse",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "close",
      "question": "proche",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "night",
      "question": "nuit",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "real",
      "question": "réel",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "life",
      "question": "vie",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "few",
      "question": "peu",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "north",
      "question": "nord",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "book",
      "question": "livre",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "carry",
      "question": "porter",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "took",
      "question": "a pris",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "science",
      "question": "science",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "eat",
      "question": "manger",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "room",
      "question": "chambre",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "friend",
      "question": "ami",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "began",
      "question": "a commencé",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "idea",
      "question": "idée",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "fish",
      "question": "poisson",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "mountain",
      "question": "montagne",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "stop",
      "question": "Arrêtez",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "once",
      "question": "une fois",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "base",
      "question": "base",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "hear",
      "question": "entendre",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "horse",
      "question": "cheval",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "cut",
      "question": "coupe",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "sure",
      "question": "sûr",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "watch",
      "question": "regarder",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "color",
      "question": "couleur",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "face",
      "question": "face",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "wood",
      "question": "bois",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "main",
      "question": "principal",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "open",
      "question": "ouvert",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "seem",
      "question": "paraître",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "together",
      "question": "ensemble",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "next",
      "question": "suivant",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "white",
      "question": "blanc",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "children",
      "question": "enfants",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "begin",
      "question": "commencer",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "got",
      "question": "eu",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "walk",
      "question": "marcher",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "example",
      "question": "exemple",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "ease",
      "question": "facilité",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "paper",
      "question": "papier",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "group",
      "question": "groupe",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "always",
      "question": "toujours",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "music",
      "question": "musique",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "those",
      "question": "ceux",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "both",
      "question": "tous les deux",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "mark",
      "question": "marque",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "often",
      "question": "souvent",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "letter",
      "question": "lettre",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "until",
      "question": "jusqu’à ce que",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "mile",
      "question": "mile",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "river",
      "question": "rivière",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "car",
      "question": "voiture",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "feet",
      "question": "pieds",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "care",
      "question": "soins",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "second",
      "question": "deuxième",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "enough",
      "question": "assez",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "plain",
      "question": "plaine",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "girl",
      "question": "fille",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "usual",
      "question": "habituel",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "young",
      "question": "jeune",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "ready",
      "question": "prêt",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "above",
      "question": "au-dessus",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "ever",
      "question": "jamais",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "red",
      "question": "rouge",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "list",
      "question": "liste",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "though",
      "question": "bien que",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "feel",
      "question": "sentir",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "talk",
      "question": "parler",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "bird",
      "question": "oiseau",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "soon",
      "question": "bientôt",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "body",
      "question": "corps",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "dog",
      "question": "chien",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "family",
      "question": "famille",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "direct",
      "question": "direct",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "pose",
      "question": "pose",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "leave",
      "question": "laisser",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "song",
      "question": "chanson",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "measure",
      "question": "mesurer",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "door",
      "question": "porte",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "product",
      "question": "produit",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "black",
      "question": "noir",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "short",
      "question": "court",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "numeral",
      "question": "chiffre",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "class",
      "question": "classe",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "wind",
      "question": "vent",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "question",
      "question": "question",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "happen",
      "question": "arriver",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "complete",
      "question": "complète",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "ship",
      "question": "navire",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "area",
      "question": "zone",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "half",
      "question": "moitié",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "rock",
      "question": "rock",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "order",
      "question": "ordre",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "fire",
      "question": "feu",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "south",
      "question": "sud",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "problem",
      "question": "problème",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "piece",
      "question": "pièce",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "told",
      "question": "dit",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "knew",
      "question": "savait",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "pass",
      "question": "passer",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "since",
      "question": "depuis",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "top",
      "question": "haut",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "whole",
      "question": "ensemble",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "king",
      "question": "roi",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "street",
      "question": "rue",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "inch",
      "question": "pouce",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "multiply",
      "question": "multiplier",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "nothing",
      "question": "rien",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "course",
      "question": "cours",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "stay",
      "question": "rester",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "wheel",
      "question": "roue",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "full",
      "question": "plein",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "force",
      "question": "force",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "blue",
      "question": "bleu",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "object",
      "question": "objet",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "decide",
      "question": "décider",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "surface",
      "question": "surface",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "deep",
      "question": "profond",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "moon",
      "question": "lune",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "island",
      "question": "île",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "foot",
      "question": "pied",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "system",
      "question": "système",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "busy",
      "question": "occupé",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "test",
      "question": "test",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "record",
      "question": "record",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "boat",
      "question": "bateau",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "common",
      "question": "commun",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "gold",
      "question": "or",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "possible",
      "question": "possible",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "plane",
      "question": "plan",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "stead",
      "question": "place",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "dry",
      "question": "sec",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "wonder",
      "question": "se demander",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "laugh",
      "question": "rire",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "thousand",
      "question": "mille",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "ago",
      "question": "il ya",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "ran",
      "question": "ran",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "check",
      "question": "vérifier",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "game",
      "question": "jeu",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "shape",
      "question": "forme",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "equate",
      "question": "assimiler",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "hot",
      "question": "chaud",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "miss",
      "question": "manquer",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "brought",
      "question": "apporté",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "heat",
      "question": "chaleur",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "snow",
      "question": "neige",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "tire",
      "question": "pneu",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "bring",
      "question": "apporter",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "yes",
      "question": "oui",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "distant",
      "question": "lointain",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "fill",
      "question": "remplir",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "east",
      "question": "est",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "paint",
      "question": "peindre",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "language",
      "question": "langue",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "among",
      "question": "entre",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "unit",
      "question": "unité",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "power",
      "question": "puissance",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "town",
      "question": "ville",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "fine",
      "question": "fin",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "certain",
      "question": "certain",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "fly",
      "question": "voler",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "fall",
      "question": "tomber",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "lead",
      "question": "conduire",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "cry",
      "question": "cri",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "dark",
      "question": "sombre",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "machine",
      "question": "machine",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "note",
      "question": "Note",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "wait",
      "question": "patienter",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "plan",
      "question": "plan",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "figure",
      "question": "figure",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "star",
      "question": "étoile",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "box",
      "question": "boîte",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "noun",
      "question": "nom",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "field",
      "question": "domaine",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "rest",
      "question": "reste",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "correct",
      "question": "correct",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "able",
      "question": "capable",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "pound",
      "question": "livre",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "done",
      "question": "Terminé",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "beauty",
      "question": "beauté",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "drive",
      "question": "entraînement",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "stood",
      "question": "résisté",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "contain",
      "question": "contenir",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "front",
      "question": "avant",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "teach",
      "question": "enseigner",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "week",
      "question": "semaine",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "final",
      "question": "finale",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "gave",
      "question": "donné",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "green",
      "question": "vert",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "oh",
      "question": "oh",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "quick",
      "question": "rapide",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "develop",
      "question": "développer",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "ocean",
      "question": "océan",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "warm",
      "question": "chaud",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "free",
      "question": "gratuit",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "minute",
      "question": "minute",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "strong",
      "question": "fort",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "special",
      "question": "spécial",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "mind",
      "question": "esprit",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "behind",
      "question": "derrière",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "clear",
      "question": "clair",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "tail",
      "question": "queue",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "produce",
      "question": "produire",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "fact",
      "question": "fait",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "space",
      "question": "espace",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "heard",
      "question": "entendu",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "best",
      "question": "meilleur",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "hour",
      "question": "heure",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "better",
      "question": "mieux",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "true",
      "question": "VRAI",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "during",
      "question": "pendant",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "hundred",
      "question": "cent",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "five",
      "question": "cinq",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "remember",
      "question": "rappeler",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "step",
      "question": "étape",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "early",
      "question": "tôt",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "hold",
      "question": "tenir",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "west",
      "question": "ouest",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "ground",
      "question": "sol",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "interest",
      "question": "intérêt",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "reach",
      "question": "atteindre",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "fast",
      "question": "rapide",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "verb",
      "question": "verbe",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "sing",
      "question": "chanter",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "listen",
      "question": "écouter",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "six",
      "question": "six",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "table",
      "question": "table",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "travel",
      "question": "Voyage",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "less",
      "question": "moins",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "morning",
      "question": "matin",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "ten",
      "question": "dix",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "simple",
      "question": "simple",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "several",
      "question": "plusieurs",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "vowel",
      "question": "voyelle",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "toward",
      "question": "vers",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "war",
      "question": "guerre",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "lay",
      "question": "poser",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "against",
      "question": "contre",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "pattern",
      "question": "modèle",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "slow",
      "question": "lent",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "center",
      "question": "centre",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "love",
      "question": "amour",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "person",
      "question": "personne",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "money",
      "question": "argent",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "serve",
      "question": "servir",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "appear",
      "question": "apparaître",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "road",
      "question": "route",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "map",
      "question": "carte",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "rain",
      "question": "pluie",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "rule",
      "question": "règle",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "govern",
      "question": "gouverner",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "pull",
      "question": "tirer",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "cold",
      "question": "froid",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "notice",
      "question": "avis",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "voice",
      "question": "voix",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "energy",
      "question": "énergie",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "hunt",
      "question": "chasse",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "probable",
      "question": "probable",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "bed",
      "question": "lit",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "brother",
      "question": "frère",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "egg",
      "question": "œuf",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "ride",
      "question": "tour",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "cell",
      "question": "cellule",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "believe",
      "question": "croire",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "perhaps",
      "question": "peut-être",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "pick",
      "question": "choisir",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "sudden",
      "question": "soudain",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "count",
      "question": "compter",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "square",
      "question": "carré",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "reason",
      "question": "raison",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "length",
      "question": "longueur",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "represent",
      "question": "représenter",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "art",
      "question": "art",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "subject",
      "question": "sujet",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "region",
      "question": "région",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "size",
      "question": "taille",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "vary",
      "question": "varier",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "settle",
      "question": "régler",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "speak",
      "question": "parler",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "weight",
      "question": "poids",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "general",
      "question": "général",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "ice",
      "question": "glace",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "matter",
      "question": "question",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "circle",
      "question": "cercle",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "pair",
      "question": "paire",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "include",
      "question": "inclure",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "divide",
      "question": "fracture",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "syllable",
      "question": "syllabe",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "felt",
      "question": "feutre",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "grand",
      "question": "grandiose",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "ball",
      "question": "balle",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "yet",
      "question": "encore",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "wave",
      "question": "vague",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "drop",
      "question": "tomber",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "heart",
      "question": "cœur",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "am",
      "question": "h",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "present",
      "question": "présent",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "heavy",
      "question": "lourd",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "dance",
      "question": "danse",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "engine",
      "question": "moteur",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "position",
      "question": "position",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "arm",
      "question": "bras",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "wide",
      "question": "large",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "sail",
      "question": "voile",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "material",
      "question": "matériel",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "fraction",
      "question": "fraction",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "forest",
      "question": "forêt",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "sit",
      "question": "s’asseoir",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "race",
      "question": "course",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "window",
      "question": "fenêtre",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "store",
      "question": "magasin",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "summer",
      "question": "été",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "train",
      "question": "train",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "sleep",
      "question": "sommeil",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "prove",
      "question": "prouver",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "lone",
      "question": "seul",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "leg",
      "question": "jambe",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "exercise",
      "question": "exercice",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "wall",
      "question": "mur",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "catch",
      "question": "capture",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "mount",
      "question": "monture",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "wish",
      "question": "souhaiter",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "sky",
      "question": "ciel",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "board",
      "question": "conseil",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "joy",
      "question": "joie",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "winter",
      "question": "hiver",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "sat",
      "question": "sat",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "written",
      "question": "écrit",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "wild",
      "question": "sauvage",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "instrument",
      "question": "instrument",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "kept",
      "question": "conservé",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "glass",
      "question": "verre",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "grass",
      "question": "herbe",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "cow",
      "question": "vache",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "job",
      "question": "emploi",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "edge",
      "question": "bord",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "sign",
      "question": "signe",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "visit",
      "question": "visite",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "past",
      "question": "passé",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "soft",
      "question": "doux",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "fun",
      "question": "amusement",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "bright",
      "question": "clair",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "gas",
      "question": "gaz",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "weather",
      "question": "temps",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "month",
      "question": "mois",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "million",
      "question": "million",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "bear",
      "question": "porter",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "finish",
      "question": "finition",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "happy",
      "question": "heureux",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "hope",
      "question": "espoir",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "flower",
      "question": "fleur",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "clothe",
      "question": "vêtir",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "strange",
      "question": "étrange",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "gone",
      "question": "disparu",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "trade",
      "question": "commerce",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "melody",
      "question": "mélodie",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "trip",
      "question": "voyage",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "office",
      "question": "bureau",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "receive",
      "question": "recevoir",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "row",
      "question": "rangée",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "mouth",
      "question": "bouche",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "exact",
      "question": "exact",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "symbol",
      "question": "symbole",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "die",
      "question": "mourir",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "least",
      "question": "moins",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "trouble",
      "question": "difficulté",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "shout",
      "question": "cri",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "except",
      "question": "sauf",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "wrote",
      "question": "écrit",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "seed",
      "question": "semence",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "tone",
      "question": "ton",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "join",
      "question": "joindre",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "suggest",
      "question": "suggérer",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "clean",
      "question": "propre",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "break",
      "question": "pause",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "lady",
      "question": "dame",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "yard",
      "question": "cour",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "rise",
      "question": "augmenter",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "bad",
      "question": "mauvais",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "blow",
      "question": "coup",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "oil",
      "question": "huile",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "blood",
      "question": "sang",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "touch",
      "question": "toucher",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "grew",
      "question": "a augmenté",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "cent",
      "question": "cent",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "mix",
      "question": "mélanger",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "team",
      "question": "équipe",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "wire",
      "question": "fil",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "cost",
      "question": "coût",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "lost",
      "question": "perdu",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "brown",
      "question": "brun",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "wear",
      "question": "porter",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "garden",
      "question": "jardin",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "equal",
      "question": "égal",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "sent",
      "question": "expédié",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "choose",
      "question": "choisir",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "fell",
      "question": "est tombé",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "fit",
      "question": "s’adapter",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "flow",
      "question": "débit",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "fair",
      "question": "juste",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "bank",
      "question": "banque",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "collect",
      "question": "recueillir",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "save",
      "question": "sauver",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "control",
      "question": "contrôle",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "decimal",
      "question": "décimal",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "ear",
      "question": "oreille",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "else",
      "question": "autre",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "quite",
      "question": "tout à fait",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "broke",
      "question": "cassé",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "case",
      "question": "cas",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "middle",
      "question": "milieu",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "kill",
      "question": "tuer",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "son",
      "question": "fils",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "lake",
      "question": "lac",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "moment",
      "question": "moment",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "scale",
      "question": "échelle",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "loud",
      "question": "fort",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "spring",
      "question": "printemps",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "observe",
      "question": "observer",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "child",
      "question": "enfant",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "straight",
      "question": "droit",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "consonant",
      "question": "consonne",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "nation",
      "question": "nation",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "dictionary",
      "question": "dictionnaire",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "milk",
      "question": "lait",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "speed",
      "question": "vitesse",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "method",
      "question": "méthode",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "organ",
      "question": "organe",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "pay",
      "question": "payer",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "age",
      "question": "âge",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "section",
      "question": "section",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "dress",
      "question": "robe",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "cloud",
      "question": "nuage",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "surprise",
      "question": "surprise",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "quiet",
      "question": "calme",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "stone",
      "question": "pierre",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "tiny",
      "question": "minuscule",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "climb",
      "question": "montée",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "cool",
      "question": "frais",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "design",
      "question": "conception",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "poor",
      "question": "pauvres",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "lot",
      "question": "lot",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "experiment",
      "question": "expérience",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "bottom",
      "question": "bas",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "key",
      "question": "clé",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "iron",
      "question": "fer",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "single",
      "question": "unique",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "stick",
      "question": "bâton",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "flat",
      "question": "plat",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "twenty",
      "question": "vingt",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "skin",
      "question": "peau",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "smile",
      "question": "sourire",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "crease",
      "question": "pli",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "hole",
      "question": "trou",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "jump",
      "question": "sauter",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "baby",
      "question": "bébé",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "eight",
      "question": "huit",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "village",
      "question": "village",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "meet",
      "question": "se rencontrent",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "root",
      "question": "racine",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "buy",
      "question": "acheter",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "raise",
      "question": "augmenter",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "solve",
      "question": "résoudre",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "metal",
      "question": "métal",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "whether",
      "question": "si",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "push",
      "question": "pousser",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "seven",
      "question": "sept",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "paragraph",
      "question": "paragraphe",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "third",
      "question": "troisième",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "shall",
      "question": "doit",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "held",
      "question": "en attente",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "hair",
      "question": "cheveux",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "describe",
      "question": "décrire",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "cook",
      "question": "cuisinier",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "floor",
      "question": "étage",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "either",
      "question": "chaque",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "result",
      "question": "résultat",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "burn",
      "question": "brûler",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "hill",
      "question": "colline",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "safe",
      "question": "coffre-fort",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "cat",
      "question": "chat",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "century",
      "question": "siècle",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "consider",
      "question": "envisager",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "type",
      "question": "type",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "law",
      "question": "droit",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "bit",
      "question": "peu",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "coast",
      "question": "côte",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "copy",
      "question": "copie",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "phrase",
      "question": "phrase",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "silent",
      "question": "silencieux",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "tall",
      "question": "haut",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "sand",
      "question": "sable",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "soil",
      "question": "sol",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "roll",
      "question": "rouleau",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "temperature",
      "question": "température",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "finger",
      "question": "doigt",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "industry",
      "question": "industrie",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "value",
      "question": "valeur",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "fight",
      "question": "lutte",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "lie",
      "question": "mensonge",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "beat",
      "question": "battre",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "excite",
      "question": "exciter",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "natural",
      "question": "naturel",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "view",
      "question": "vue",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "sense",
      "question": "sens",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "capital",
      "question": "capital",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "won’t",
      "question": "ne sera pas",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "chair",
      "question": "chaise",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "danger",
      "question": "danger",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "fruit",
      "question": "fruit",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "rich",
      "question": "riche",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "thick",
      "question": "épais",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "soldier",
      "question": "soldat",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "process",
      "question": "processus",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "operate",
      "question": "fonctionner",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "practice",
      "question": "pratique",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "separate",
      "question": "séparé",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "difficult",
      "question": "difficile",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "doctor",
      "question": "médecin",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "please",
      "question": "s’il vous plaît",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "protect",
      "question": "protéger",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "noon",
      "question": "midi",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "crop",
      "question": "récolte",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "modern",
      "question": "moderne",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "element",
      "question": "élément",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "hit",
      "question": "frapper",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "student",
      "question": "étudiant",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "corner",
      "question": "coin",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "party",
      "question": "partie",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "supply",
      "question": "alimentation",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "whose",
      "question": "dont",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "locate",
      "question": "localiser",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "ring",
      "question": "anneau",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "character",
      "question": "caractère",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "insect",
      "question": "insecte",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "caught",
      "question": "pris",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "period",
      "question": "période",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "indicate",
      "question": "indiquer",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "radio",
      "question": "radio",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "spoke",
      "question": "rayon",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "atom",
      "question": "atome",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "human",
      "question": "humain",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "history",
      "question": "histoire",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "effect",
      "question": "effet",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "electric",
      "question": "électrique",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "expect",
      "question": "attendre",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "bone",
      "question": "os",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "rail",
      "question": "rail",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "imagine",
      "question": "imaginer",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "provide",
      "question": "fournir",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "agree",
      "question": "se mettre d’accord",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "thus",
      "question": "ainsi",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "gentle",
      "question": "doux",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "woman",
      "question": "femme",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "captain",
      "question": "capitaine",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "guess",
      "question": "deviner",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "necessary",
      "question": "nécessaire",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "sharp",
      "question": "net",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "wing",
      "question": "aile",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "create",
      "question": "créer",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "neighbor",
      "question": "voisin",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "wash",
      "question": "lavage",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "bat",
      "question": "chauve-souris",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "rather",
      "question": "plutôt",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "crowd",
      "question": "foule",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "corn",
      "question": "blé",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "compare",
      "question": "comparer",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "poem",
      "question": "poème",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "string",
      "question": "chaîne",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "bell",
      "question": "cloche",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "depend",
      "question": "dépendre",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "meat",
      "question": "viande",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "rub",
      "question": "rub",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "tube",
      "question": "tube",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "famous",
      "question": "célèbre",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "dollar",
      "question": "dollar",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "stream",
      "question": "courant",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "fear",
      "question": "peur",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "sight",
      "question": "vue",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "thin",
      "question": "mince",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "triangle",
      "question": "triangle",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "planet",
      "question": "planète",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "hurry",
      "question": "se dépêcher",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "chief",
      "question": "chef",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "colony",
      "question": "colonie",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "clock",
      "question": "horloge",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "mine",
      "question": "mine",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "tie",
      "question": "lien",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "enter",
      "question": "entrer",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "major",
      "question": "majeur",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "fresh",
      "question": "frais",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "search",
      "question": "recherche",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "send",
      "question": "envoyer",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "yellow",
      "question": "jaune",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "gun",
      "question": "pistolet",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "allow",
      "question": "permettre",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "print",
      "question": "impression",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "dead",
      "question": "mort",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "spot",
      "question": "place",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "desert",
      "question": "désert",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "suit",
      "question": "costume",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "current",
      "question": "courant",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "lift",
      "question": "ascenseur",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "rose",
      "question": "rose",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "arrive",
      "question": "arriver",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "master",
      "question": "maître",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "track",
      "question": "piste",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "parent",
      "question": "mère",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "shore",
      "question": "rivage",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "division",
      "question": "division",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "sheet",
      "question": "feuille",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "substance",
      "question": "substance",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "favor",
      "question": "favoriser",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "connect",
      "question": "relier",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "post",
      "question": "poste",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "spend",
      "question": "passer",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "chord",
      "question": "corde",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "fat",
      "question": "graisse",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "glad",
      "question": "heureux",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "original",
      "question": "original",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "share",
      "question": "part",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "station",
      "question": "station",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "dad",
      "question": "papa",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "bread",
      "question": "pain",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "charge",
      "question": "charger",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "proper",
      "question": "propre",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "bar",
      "question": "bar",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "offer",
      "question": "proposition",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "segment",
      "question": "segment",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "slave",
      "question": "esclave",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "duck",
      "question": "canard",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "instant",
      "question": "instant",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "market",
      "question": "marché",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "degree",
      "question": "degré",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "populate",
      "question": "peupler",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "chick",
      "question": "poussin",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "dear",
      "question": "cher",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "enemy",
      "question": "ennemi",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "reply",
      "question": "répondre",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "drink",
      "question": "boisson",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "occur",
      "question": "se produire",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "support",
      "question": "support",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "speech",
      "question": "discours",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "nature",
      "question": "nature",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "range",
      "question": "gamme",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "steam",
      "question": "vapeur",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "motion",
      "question": "mouvement",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "path",
      "question": "chemin",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "liquid",
      "question": "liquide",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "log",
      "question": "enregistrer",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "meant",
      "question": "signifiait",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "quotient",
      "question": "quotient",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "teeth",
      "question": "dents",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "shell",
      "question": "coquille",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "neck",
      "question": "cou",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "oxygen",
      "question": "oxygène",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "sugar",
      "question": "sucre",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "death",
      "question": "décès",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "pretty",
      "question": "assez",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "skill",
      "question": "compétence",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "women",
      "question": "femmes",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "season",
      "question": "saison",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "solution",
      "question": "solution",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "magnet",
      "question": "aimant",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "silver",
      "question": "argent",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "thank",
      "question": "merci",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "branch",
      "question": "branche",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "match",
      "question": "rencontre",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "suffix",
      "question": "suffixe",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "especially",
      "question": "particulièrement",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "fig",
      "question": "figue",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "afraid",
      "question": "peur",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "huge",
      "question": "énorme",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "sister",
      "question": "sœur",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "steel",
      "question": "acier",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "discuss",
      "question": "discuter",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "forward",
      "question": "avant",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "similar",
      "question": "similaire",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "guide",
      "question": "guider",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "experience",
      "question": "expérience",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "score",
      "question": "score",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "apple",
      "question": "pomme",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "bought",
      "question": "acheté",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "led",
      "question": "LED",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "pitch",
      "question": "pas",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "coat",
      "question": "manteau",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "mass",
      "question": "masse",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "card",
      "question": "carte",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "band",
      "question": "bande",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "rope",
      "question": "corde",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "slip",
      "question": "glissement",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "win",
      "question": "gagner",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "dream",
      "question": "rêver",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "evening",
      "question": "soirée",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "condition",
      "question": "condition",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "feed",
      "question": "alimentation",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "tool",
      "question": "outil",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "total",
      "question": "total",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "basic",
      "question": "de base",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "smell",
      "question": "odeur",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "valley",
      "question": "vallée",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "nor",
      "question": "ni",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "double",
      "question": "double",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "seat",
      "question": "siège",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "continue",
      "question": "continuer",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "block",
      "question": "bloc",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "chart",
      "question": "graphique",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "hat",
      "question": "chapeau",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "sell",
      "question": "vendre",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "success",
      "question": "succès",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "company",
      "question": "entreprise",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "subtract",
      "question": "soustraire",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "event",
      "question": "événement",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "particular",
      "question": "particulier",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "deal",
      "question": "accord",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "swim",
      "question": "baignade",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "term",
      "question": "terme",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "opposite",
      "question": "opposé",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "wife",
      "question": "femme",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "shoe",
      "question": "chaussure",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "shoulder",
      "question": "épaule",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "spread",
      "question": "propagation",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "arrange",
      "question": "organiser",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "camp",
      "question": "camp",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "invent",
      "question": "inventer",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "cotton",
      "question": "coton",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "born",
      "question": "né",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "determine",
      "question": "déterminer",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "quart",
      "question": "litre",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "nine",
      "question": "neuf",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "truck",
      "question": "camion",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "noise",
      "question": "bruit",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "level",
      "question": "niveau",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "chance",
      "question": "chance",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "gather",
      "question": "recueillir",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "shop",
      "question": "boutique",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "stretch",
      "question": "tronçon",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "throw",
      "question": "jeter",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "shine",
      "question": "éclat",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "property",
      "question": "propriété",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "column",
      "question": "colonne",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "molecule",
      "question": "molécule",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "select",
      "question": "sélectionner",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "wrong",
      "question": "mal",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "gray",
      "question": "gris",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "repeat",
      "question": "répétition",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "require",
      "question": "exiger",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "broad",
      "question": "large",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "prepare",
      "question": "préparer",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "salt",
      "question": "sel",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "nose",
      "question": "nez",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "plural",
      "question": "pluriel",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "anger",
      "question": "colère",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "claim",
      "question": "revendication",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "continent",
      "question": "continent",
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ]
    }
  ],
  "language_1": "fr",
  "subject": "learn_english_1000_words",
  "language_2": "en",
  "type": "BUTTON",
  "sentence": null
}
